which must drive his opponents crazy because even the sneaker thing i was on social media last night
very interesting as you see black support eroding from joe biden this is connecting with black
america because they love sneakers they're into sneakers they love the you know this is a big
deal certainly in in the inner city so when you have trump roll out his sneaker line they're like
wait a minute this is cool he's reaching them on a level that defies and is above politics
but culture always trumps politics and trump understands culture like no politician i've
ever seen question for that's what they think of you they think you are a sneaker buying fool
that's what they think of you they think you are a sneaker buying fool
bridge they think you are a sneaker nigga
a sneaker nigga they think you are a sneaker nigga
that's what they think of us let's prove otherwise these people are crazy
translation they're too dumb to know about politics so just keep distracting them with dumb shit
hey yo why they ain't pass that george floyd bill yet hey terrell
ahhh